Md. Abul Hasan Sumon



CONTACT

+8801783614779



sumon.hasan0009@gmail.com



House: 19, Road: 08, Section: 10, Block: A, Mirpur, Dhaka



www.linkedin.com/in/abul-hasan-sumon-45b834158/

in

EDUCATION

2011 - 2014

BBA, MARKETING Green University of Bangladesh, Dhaka Score: 3.86

KEY SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator



Microsoft Office Suite



Team Leadership



English / Hindi



AWARDS

November 2015

First Runners-up, Gazipur Sales Development Campaign OPPO Bangladesh

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Marketing Manager with 1.5 year of experience in smartphone & feature phone, 12 months' experience as Marketing Executive.

Management: Recruited, hired, and trained marketing and sales executive

Achievement: Directed launch of 5 new model of smartphone in Bangladesh.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2019 (May) - Present

MARKETING MANAGER

LAVA International (Bangladesh) Limited, 2019(May) - Present

- Developed new promotional campaign, increasing sales revenue.
- Negotiated new contracts with vendors, for the ATL/BTL marketing.
- Recruited, hired, and trained marketing executive
- Creating and maintaining a healthy relationship with corporate partners

2018 - 2019

MARKETING Executive

LAVA International (Bangladesh) Limited, 2018 - 2019

- Managed all marketing functions, including brand management, product launch, advertising, marketing collateral, and events
- Negotiated existing and new vendors for ATL/BTL marketing
- National retail brand development and housekeeping.
- Developed, designed new ideas and implemented in Filed force and social platform.

2014-2018

Sales Executive

OPPO Bangladesh Equipment Co. Ltd.

- Ensured 75% average sell out vs target.
- Responsible for primary, secondary and tertiary sell out.
- Developed new sales channel, dealer.
- Recruited, hired, and trained Field sales people and maintained over 100 people at a time.
- Developed new market.